<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi= "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
    <id>spreedboxlicensekeys</id>
    <name>Spreedbox License Keys</name>
    <summary>An app that can be used to manage the additional software license keys of a Spreedbox</summary>
    <description><![CDATA[An app that can be used to manage the additional software license keys of a Spreedbox

License keys are bound to the hardware, so they have to be requested from the Spreedbox where they will be used later.

Features

The following features are available through the app:

Request a new license
Install a license
List installed licenses
Request a new license

To request a license, some information about the user have to be given:

The name (string, required)
The company (string, optional)
The street (string, required)
The zipcode and city (string, required)
The two-letter country code (string, required)
The phone number (string, optional)
The email address (string, required)
The app will send this data to the backend service (see below) which will generate a license request (string). This license request must then be sent to us, will be updated to contain information about the available features, will be signed and returned to the requester.

Afterwards, the license can be installed and the included features will be enabled on the Spreedbox.

Install a license

The app provides a way to either upload the license file or to paste the license text in some field to install it.

The license data is sent to the backend service (see below) which will verify the license, check if it is valid for the current hardware and then install it in the system.

List installed licenses

The app provides an overview to list all installed licenses and also shows the available features.]]></description>
    <licence>agpl</licence>
    <author mail="peter.edens@spreedbox.me" >Peter Edens</author>
    <version>0.0.1</version>
    <namespace>SpreedboxLicenseKeys</namespace>
    <category>tools</category>
    <dependencies>
        <nextcloud min-version="10"/>
    </dependencies>
</info>
